<J0SHUA JHUN DE ANDRES S0FTWARE_DEVEL0PER>

github.com/joshuajhun
in linkedin.com/in/joshuajhun
in joshuajhun@gmail.com

858-722-7866

PR0FILE

Passionate developer who loves using technology and software to better the human experience. Excited to join a team that fosters good programming practices and will allow me to grow as developer through mentorship, continued learning and valued contribution to internal tools and projects.

SKTLLS

Ruby 2.X Rails 4.X JavaScript iQuery Active Record Sinatra TDD MiniTest/RSpec HTML CSS Boostrap Materialize

PHOTOSHOP ILLUSTRATOR LIGHTROOM

PRØJECTS

TRELORA Leaderboard | github.com/joshuajhun/TRELORA_Leaderboard

This is a JavaScript application living inside a Rails shell. This application displays information coming from TRELORA's internal API. The application is making staggered API calls [AJAX] and the dynamic background will change based on the weather[jQuery]. [paired project]

Ticketly || ticketly.herokuapp.com || github.com/joshuajhun/ticketly

We inherited old code and pivoted it to become a multi-tenancy store that sells tickets. I hand-rolled the authorization and authentication and also implemented BigVideo.JS for the dynamic video in the background. [group project]

Electron OCR || github.com/joshuajhun/electron-orc || npmjs.com/package/electron-ocr

This is a Electron.js application [desktop] that utilizes OCR technology. In this application you can upload a photo with text and the application will pull out the text from the photograph for you instantly. The application is also an NPM node module. I was responsible for building out the Electron shell and implementing the OCR library. [paired project]

EXPERIENCE

Teacher/Mentor Colorado Uplift Denver, CO 10/2013 - 8/2015

- + Responsible for creating and implementing weekly lesson plans for students
- + Coordinated logistics for international trips and local camps for up to 150 students
- + Produced creative assets for organization, including videos, graphic design, and photos

Web Designer / Web Master University of Denver Human Trafficking Center (HTC) 9/2014 - 5/2015

- + Used HTML/CSS, Wordpress, and Adobe Creative Suite to manage website.
- + Migrated previous website content to new Wordpress design template.
- + Created and managed graphic content and designed layout for all webpages to create a tactful user interface and experience.
- + Assisted HTC Marketing Coordinator in branding the HTC across all online media platforms

Student Support Fellowship Turing School Denver, CO 3/2016- Current

- + Meet weekly with students to review code and talk about best coding practices.
- + Review fundamental Ruby, Rails, and Javascript concepts with students durring pairing sessions.
- + Troubleshoot and collaborate with fellow students to debug and problem solve issues within the code base.
- + Aggregate data for instructors to review to better understand student performance and academic retention.

EDUCATION

Turing School of Software and Design (Denver, CO) March 2016
Certificate in Web Application Development with Ruby, Rails and JavaScript